

POP ADRIAN BOGDAN

Assistant Store Manager - Media Galaxy Cluj Napoca - Altex Romania SRL

Age 33 from Cluj Napoca, not married -

Contact details

Email: popadrianbogdan@yahoo.com Tel: 0747362453

Address: Henri Barbusse

Professional objective

Although my professional experience is in the field of online and retail sales management, I am currently in the process of a major career change in the direction of web development.

I am self-taught and have acquired basic knowledge of the following: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP-MySql, Phpmyadmin, Symphony Framework and Git.

I am highly motivated and enthusiastic, hardworking always with excellent attention to detail. I am enclosing my resume for your consideration, also for more detailed information about my level of expertise you can review some of my personal projects at https://www.github.com/fildes3d3.

Professional experience

Experience by departments

IT Hardware: 4 months

Internet / e-Commerce: 10 months Sales: 9 years and 11 months

Apr 2014 - present

2 years and 1 month

Assistant Store Manager - Media Galaxy Cluj Napoca - Altex Romania SRL

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | IT / Telecom

- -general store management (representation of the company in relation to the local authorities, merchandising)
- -optimizing the store profitability
- -supervizing the visual identity of the store
- -Planning resources (employees, working timetable, local budgets)
- -team management (task assignment, motivation, training, coaching and control);
- -employees selection and recruitment
- -sales reports

Oct 2009 - Nov 2013

Showroom Manager - Dante International SA www.emag.ro

4 years and 2 months

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | IT / Telecom

- -NPS, Customer Care, Customer Satisfaction, NPS analysis, monitoring an optimizations at national level, customer feedback questionnaires, phone client feedback
- -Identifying new locations for expanding the showroom network at regional level, new location set-up, actively involved in personal recruitment, operational, procedural and sales training for new employees
- -General showroom management (representation of the company in relation to the local authorities, merchandising)
- -Maintaining a high standard of customer services, showroom image and solving unexpected problems
- -Planning resources (employees, working timetable, local budgets)
- -team management (task assignment, motivation, training, coaching and control); -employees selection and

recruitment

- I have developed a strong efficient team for the Cluj Napoca Showroom
- -I specialized in the analysis, monitoring and optimization at a national level, for the Customer Care/ Customer Satisfaction policies, based on the existing feedback system (Customer feedback questionnaires, out-interviews, customer phone feedback, NPS scores)

Phone

Laptop

Mediacl Benefits

May 2008 - May 2009

Account Manager - Falmingo Computers SA-Flamingo Distribution Centre - FDC

1 year and 1 month

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | -

- -achieving monthly sales targets
- -compiling, verifying sales reports to upper management
- -maintaining a good relationship with local authorities

Jul 2005 - May 2008

Store Manager - Flamingo International SA - Flamingo Computers

2 years and 11 months

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | -

- -new location set-up, actively involved in personal recruitment, operational, procedural and sales training for new employees
- -General showroom management (representation of the company in relation to the local authorities, merchandising)
- -Maintaining a high standard of customer services, showroom image and solving unexpected problems
- -Planning resources (employees, working timetable, local budgets)
- -Team management (task assignment, motivation, training, coaching and control); -employees selection and recruitment

Diana Oancea - Area Sales Manager tel.:0740178447

Mar 2005 - Jul 2005

Service Tehnician - Flamingo International SA - Flamingo Computers

5 months

Baia Mare | IT Hardware | -

-warranty and post-warranty services, maintaining the store computers and network, logistics and merchandising

Corina Griga Shop Manager Baia Mare

tel: 0743.161.627

Nov 2001 - Sep 2002

Internet Caffe operator Service Engineer/System Maintenance - SC Golden Rule SRL

11 months

Baia Mare | Internet / e-Commerce | Media / Internet

- computer service, computer maintenance, network maintenance, Internet CaffeOperator
- The improvement of computer network whit low budget, finding efficient solutionsfor upgrading the computers cost-efficiently

Education

2001 - 2005 College / Bachelor's degree - Universitatea de Vest 'Vasile Goldis

Marketing | Baia Mare

1997 - 2001 High School - Grup Scolar Tehnic Nr.1

Electronica si Electrotehnica - Electronist Tehnica de Calcul | Baia Mare

Foreign languages

English - Advanced, Italian - Medium, French - Medium

Other info

Numerous sales trainings (Microsoft, Intel, Samsung, HP, Apple, Customer Satisfaction, Sales Excellence)

Driving license

Categories A, B

acquired on 05 Nov 2002